Faculty Minutes RG.018
Poly Archives & Special Collections at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
- Series III: Boxes, 1986 - present
  - Faculty Minutes, November 7, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 7, 2012 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 5, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 5, 2012 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 6, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 6, 2013 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 6, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 6, 2013 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Mintues, April 10, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 10, 2013 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 1, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 1, 2013 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 11, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Mintues, September 11, 2013 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 2, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 6, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 6, 2013 (duplicates) (Box 21, Folder 21)